Guide to the Trade catalogs collection.
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- M
  - McCray Refrigerator Sales Corporation (Kendallville, Ind.), 1901–1935; Uai +M138; 6 volumes (Box 181, Folder 2168)
    Refrigerators, etc.
  - McCullough, W. T., Electric Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1927; Uai +M1389; 1 volume (Box 181, Folder 2169)
    Electrical supplies
  - McCullough-Dalzell Crucible Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1923; Uai M139; 1 volume (Box 181, Folder 2170)
    Crucibles
  - McCutcheon, James, and Company (New York, N.Y.), 1914; Uai +M1396; 1 volume (Box 181, Folder 2171)
    Linens
  - McDermott and Berea Stone Company (Berea, Ohio, etc.), 1886; Uai M143; 1 volume (Box 181, Folder 2172)
    Building stone
  - McDowell Manufacturing Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1905; Uai M148; 1 volume (Box 181, Folder 2173)
    Steel wall ties and wall plugs
  - McFaddin, H. G., and Company, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1937–1938; Uai +M161; 3 volumes (Box 181, Folder 2176)
    "Emeralite" and "Thermolite" lamps, etc.
  - McGowan Pump Company (Cincinnati, Ohio), undated; Uai M177; 1 volume (Box 181, Folder 2177)
    Water station supplies, etc.
  - McGraw Electric Company (Minneapolis, Minn.), 1937; Uai +M178; 2 volumes (Box 181, Folder 2178)
    "Toastmaster" products
  - McHugh, Joseph P., Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1919; Uai M186; 1 volume (Box 181, Folder 2181)
  - McIntosh and Seymour Corporation (Auburn, N.Y.), 1925–1929; Uai +M188; 6 volumes (Box 181, Folder 2182-2184)
    Diesel engines
  - McKesson and Robbins, Inc. (Bridgeport, Conn.), 1939; Uai +M199; 2 volumes (Box 181, Folder 2185)
  - McKibbin, George, and Son (Brooklyn, N.Y.), 1930; Uai +M21; 1 volume (Box 181, Folder 2186)
    Book binding
  - McLeod Railroad Air Signal Company (Boston, Mass.), 1885; Uai M2254; 1 volume (Box 181, Folder 2188)
    Automatic railroad signal system
  - McLeod and Henry Company (Troy, N.Y.), 1889–1904; Uai M2251; 2 volumes (Box 181, Folder 2187)
    Fire brick, tile, etc.
  - McMahan, Porter and Company (New Cumberland, W. Va.), 1886; Uai M227; 1 volume (Box 181, Folder 2189)
    Sewer pipe, fire brick, etc.
  - McMenamin and Company (Hampton, Va.), undated; Uai +M228; 2 volumes (Box 181, Folder 2190)
    Deviled crab meat
  - McMillan Book Company (Syracuse, N.Y.), 1950; Uai +M229; 1 volume (Box 181, Folder 2191)
    Loose leaf forms and binders
  - McNab and Harlin Manufacturing Company (New York, N.Y.), 1911; Uai M23; 2 volumes (Box 181, Folder 2192)
    Steel and iron fittings, etc.
  - McNally Pittsburg Manufacturing Corporation (Pittsburg, Kan.), 1947; Uai +M233; 4 volumes (Box 181, Folder 2193)
    Coal crushers and breakers, etc.
  - McShane, Henry, Manufacturing Company (Baltimore, Md.), undated; Uai M248; 1 volume (Box 181, Folder 2194)
    Bells, chimes, etc.
  - Meachum, E. C., Arms Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1891; Uai +M46; 2 volumes (Box 183, Folder 2286)
    Guns, carriages, athletic goods, etc.
  - Mead Johnson and Company (Jersey City, N.J.), 1939; Uai M4618; 2 volumes (Box 183, Folder 2289)
    Dextri-maltose
  - Mead Sales Company (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai +M4613; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2287)
    Mead papers
  - Mead, W. F., and Deverell (London, England), 1883–1884; Uai M4615; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2288)
    Christmas novelties
  - Meares, Richard (New York, N.Y.), 1875; 1 volume (Box 399, Folder 4327)
  - Meccano Company, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1914–1915; Uai +M464; 2 volumes (Box 183, Folder 2290)
    Toy construction sets
  - Mechanical Educator Company (Cleveland, Ohio), 1911; Uai M4652; 3 volumes (Box 183, Folder 2291)
    Rapid addition reader
  - Mechanical Rubber Company (Cleveland, Ohio), 1923; Uai M4657; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2292)
    Gaskets, packings, etc.
  - Medart Patent Pulley Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1902; Uai M467; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2293)
    Pulleys, clutches, hangers, etc.
  - Medford Fancy Goods Company (New York, N.Y.), 1886; Uai M468; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2294)
    Dog collars and dog furnishings
  - Meigs, M. (Washington, D. C.), 1876; Uai M476; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2295)
    Diotropic water light
  - Meilink, C. F. (Toledo, Ohio), 1925–1927; Uai +M477; 2 volumes (Box 183, Folder 2296)
    Fire proof safes
  - Menchen, Joseph, Electrical Company (New York, N.Y.), 1906; Uai +M522; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2297)
    Electrical theatrical appliances
  - Mendel, Charles (Paris, France), 1908; Uai +M5228; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2298)
  - Meneely Bell Company (Troy, N.Y.), 1896; Uai +M5243; 2 volumes (Box 183, Folder 2301)
    Bells, etc.
  - Meneely and Company (West Troy, N.Y.), 1881; Uai M52422; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2300)
  - Meneely's, Andrew, Sons (West Troy, N.Y.), 1860; Uai M5244; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2302)
  - Meneely, Clinton H., Bell Company (Troy, N.Y.), 1884; Uai +M5242; 3 volumes (Box 183, Folder 2299)
  - Merchant and Company (New York, N.Y.), 1892; Uai M5352; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2303)
    Metal tiles
  - Merchant and Evans Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1908; Uai M5354; 2 volumes (Box 183, Folder 2304)
    Roofing plates, tiles, ventilators, metal fire doors, etc.
  - Merck and Company, Inc. (Rahway, N.J.), 1907–1947; Uai M537; 5 volumes (Box 187, Folder 2475-2476)
  - Meriden Press and Drop Company (Meriden, Conn.), undated; Uai M544; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2305)
    Metal working machinery, etc.
  - Merkle Machinery Company (Kansas City, Mo.), 1921; Uai M546; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2306)
    Electrical equipment, water works equipment, etc.
  - Merriam Manufacturing Company (Durham, Conn.), 1908; Uai M551; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2307)
    Cash and bond boxes
  - Merrill Company (Boston, Mass.), 1926; Uai M552; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2308)
  - Merritt Electric Company (Middleton, Mass.), 1897; Uai M554; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2309)
  - Merritt and Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1901–1911; Uai +M553; 8 volumes (Box 204)
    Air-lock sluiceways, iron and wire work, etc.
  - Merrow Machine Company (Hartford, Conn.), 1906–1920; Uai M555; 1 volume (Box 205)
    Overedge, over seaming and shell stitch machinery, etc.
  - Mersick, C. S., and Company (New Haven, Conn.), Uai M556
    Plumbing supplies, Electrical supplies, Industrial supplies, etc.
    - 1914–1941, 6 volumes (Box 188, Folder 2477-2481)
    - 1910, 1 volume (Box 189)
    - undated, 1 volume (Box 190)
    - 1916, 1 volume (Box 191)
    - 1920, 1 volume (Box 192)
    - 1925, 1 volume (Box 193)
    - undated, 1 volume (Box 194)
    - 1945, 1 volume (Box 195)
    - 1945, 1 volume (Box 196)
  - Mertz's, George, Sons (Port Chester, N.Y.), 1902; Uai +M558; 2 volumes (Box 183, Folder 2310)
    Patent turned art moldings in wood and metal, etc.
  - Merwin, Hulbert and Company (New York, N.Y.), 1889–1892; Uai +M559; 3 volumes (Box 183, Folder 2311-2313)
    Firearms and ammunition, Gymnasium apparatus
  - Merz Engineering Company (Indianapolis, Ind.), 1947; Uai +M56; 3 volumes (Box 183, Folder 2314)
    Gages and measuring machines
  - Metal Aircraft Corporation (Cincinnati, Ohio), undated; Uai +M564; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2315)
    "Flamingo" aircraft
  - Metal Craft Company (New Haven, Conn.), 1940; Uai +M5642; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2316)
  - Metal Cutting Tools Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1949; Uai +M56425; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2317)
    High speed cutting tools
  - Metal Lath Manufacturers Association (Chicago, Ill.), 1935–1937; Uai +M5643; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2318)
    Metal lath for homes
  - Metal Office Furniture Company (Grand Rapids, Mich.), undated; Uai +M5644; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2319)
    Business equipment and office furniture
  - Metal Products and Supply Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1923; Uai M5645; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2320)
    Iron products, etc.
  - Metal Stamping Company (Jackson, Mich.), 1910; Uai +M5648; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2321)
    "White Frost" refrigerators
  - Metropolitan Greenhouse Manufacturing Company (Brooklyn, N.Y.), undated; Uai M5671; 2 volumes (Box 183, Folder 2322)
    Greenhouse parts and accessories, boilers, fittings, pipe valves, etc.
  - Meyer Scale and Hardware Company (Newark, N.J.), 1900–1923; Uai M5765; 3 volumes (Box 183, Folder 2324-2325)
    Scales, trucks, barrows, etc.
  - Meyer, Curt W. (New York, N.Y.), 1882; Uai M576; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2323)
    Chemical and meteorological supplies, etc.
  - Meyer-Sniffen Company (New York, N.Y., etc.), 1884; Uai +M5767; 2 volumes (Box 183, Folder 2326)
    Water-closet and bathing arrangements
  - Meyerowitz Brothers (New York, N.Y.), 1880; Uai +M5781; 2 volumes (Box 183, Folder 2328)
  - Meyrowitz, E. B. (New York, N.Y.), 1908–1917; Uai +M578; 4 volumes (Box 183, Folder 2327)
    X-ray and electro-therapeutical appliances
  - Mi-co Meter Company (Covington, Ky.), 1942; Uai +M5814; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2332)
    Parking meters
  - Miami Cycle and Manufacturing Company (Middletown, Ohio), 1902; Uai M58; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2329)
  - Mianus Motor Works (Stamford, Conn.), 1913; Uai M580; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2330)
    Marine motors
  - Mica Insulator Company (New York, N.Y.), 1928; Uai M581; 4 volumes (Box 183, Folder 2331)
    Electrical insulating materials
  - Michigan Aero Engine Corporation (Lansing, Mich.), undated; Uai M5815; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2333)
    Aviation rover engine
  - Michigan Bolt and Nut Works (Detroit, Mich.), 1887; Uai M5821; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2334)
    Nuts, bolts, etc.
  - Michigan Brass and Iron Works (Detroit, Mich.), 1899; Uai M5822; 1 volume (Box 183, Folder 2335)
    Valves, etc.
  - Michigan Engine Valve Company (Detroit, Mich.), 1914; Uai M5824; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2336)
    Howarth reversible sash centers
  - Michigan Stove Company (Detroit, Mich.), 1875; Uai +M5828; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2337)
  - Midland Poultry Food Company (Kansas City, Mo.), 1903; Uai M584; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2338)
    Poultry feed
  - Midvale Steel Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1915–1923; Uai M585; 2 volumes (Box 184, Folder 2339)
    Guns and mounts, Tool steel, etc.
  - Midwest Piping and Supply Company, Inc. (St. Louis, Mo.), 1930; Uai +M5853; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2340)
    Piping
  - Miehlmann, Oscar (Hamburg, Germany), 1910; Uai M5855; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2341)
    Photographic supplies and parts
  - Miles Machinery Company (Saginaw, Mich.), undated; Uai M591; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2342)
  - Millar, Charles, and Son (Utica, N.Y.), 1868–1905; Uai M611; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2343)
    Bathtubs, etc.
  - Miller Manufacturing Company (Torrington, Conn.), 1899; Uai M6155; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2347)
    Carbide lamps
  - Miller Train Control Corporation (Danville, Ill.), 1916; Uai +M616; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2348)
    Miller train control and ramp
  - Miller and Brothers (New York, N.Y.), 1868; Uai +M6142; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2344)
  - Miller and Hanimann (Brooklyn, N.Y.), undated; Uai M6146; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2345)
    Automatic baby carriage brake
  - Miller's, Jacob, Sons Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), undated; Uai M617; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2349)
    Shirts, etc.
  - Miller, Herman, Furniture Company (Zeeland, Mich.), undated; Uai +M612; 1 volume (Box 206)
  - Miller-Knoblock Wagon Company (South Bend, Ind.), 1893; Uai M615; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2346)
    Sprinkling wagons
  - Millers Falls Company (Millers Falls, Mass., etc.), 1908–1940; Uai M6175; 6 volumes (Box 184, Folder 2350-2351)
    Tools and light machinery
  - Milligan, C. T. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1879–1893; Uai +M62; 4 volumes (Box 184, Folder 2352-2353)
    Magic lantern apparatus and slides, etc.
  - Mills, Thos., and Brother, Inc. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1914; Uai M628; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2354)
    Ice cream manufacturers' tools, etc.
  - Mills, William, and Son (New York, N.Y.), 1915–1940; Uai M629; 14 volumes (Box 184, Folder 2355-2358)
  - Milner, Thomas, and Son (Liverpool, England), 1851; Uai M636; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2359)
    Safes and boxes
  - Miltimore Car Axle Company (New York, N.Y.), 1875; Uai M641; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2360)
    Car axles
  - Milton Manufacturing Company (Milton, Pa.), 1904; Uai M644; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2361)
  - Mine Safety Appliances Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1945; Uai +M66; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2362)
    Safety equipment
  - Miner and Peck Manufacturing Company (New Haven, Conn.), 1905; Uai M662; 2 volumes (Box 184, Folder 2363)
    Drop lifter, drop presses, etc.
  - Minneapolis Esterly Harvester Company (Minneapolis, Minn.), 1893; Uai M666; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2364)
  - Minneapolis Harvester Works (Minneapolis, Minn.), 1876; Uai M667; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2365)
    Harvester and twine binder
  - Minton, Hollins, and Company (Stoke-upon-Trent, England), 1899; Uai +M668; 4 volumes (Box 207)
    Tiles
  - Mississippi Glass Company (New York, N.Y., etc.), 1896; Uai M689; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2366)
    Wire glass
  - Mississippi Wire Glass Company (New York, N.Y.), 1908–1916; Uai +M69; 3 volumes (Box 184, Folder 2367-2368)
    Exemplars, wire glass, etc.
  - Mitchell and Ness (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1931; Uai +M696; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2370)
    Football equipment
  - Mitchell, Charles L., M. D. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1937; Uai M692; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2369)
    Medication for venereal diseases
  - Mitchell-Rand Insulation Company (New York, N.Y.), 1949–1953; Uai +M697; 4 volumes (Box 184, Folder 2371-2372)
  - Mix and Genest, A. G. (Berlin-Schöneberg, Germany), 1934; Uai +M6994; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2374)
    Telephone apparatus
  - Mix, G. I., and Company (New York, N.Y.), 1876; Uai M699; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2373)
    Iron goods and Britannia ware
  - Mobile Company of American (Tarrytown-on-the-Hudson, N.Y.), 1900; Uai M713; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2375)
  - Model Heating Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1895; Uai M716; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2376)
    "Novelty" boilers
  - Model Press Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), undated; Uai M719; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2377)
    Printing presses
  - Model Stoker Company (Dayton, Ohio), 1909; Uai M72; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2378)
    Automatic smokeless furnaces
  - Modern Tool Company (Erie, Pa.), 1913; Uai +M721; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2379)
    "Modern" universal grinding machines
  - Moeller Instrument Company (New York, N.Y.), 1943; Uai +M7224; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2381)
    Thermometers, hydrometers, etc.
  - Mogg, L. N. (Marcellus, N.Y.), 1900; Uai M724; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2382)
    Rifle telescopes
  - Moloney Electric Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1928–1945; Uai +M738; 6 volumes (Box 184, Folder 2383-2384)
  - Monarch Cycle Manufacturing Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1897–1899; Uai M742; 4 volumes (Box 184, Folder 2385)
  - Monarch Engineering and Manufacturing Company (Baltimore, Md.), 1918; Uai +M7422; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2386)
    Melting and heating furnaces, etc.
  - Monarch Machine Tool Company (Sidney, Ohio), 1944–1949; Uai +M7423; 2 volumes (Box 184, Folder 2387)
    Air-gage tracer, lathes, etc.
  - Monarch Manufacturing Company (Detroit, Mich.), 1914–1915; Uai M7425; 2 volumes (Box 184, Folder 2388)
    Builders' hardware, friction sashes, etc.
  - Monarch Note Book Company (St. Joseph, Mo.), 1918; Uai M7427; 2 volumes (Box 184, Folder 2389)
    Note books
  - Monarch Typewriter Company (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai M7429; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2390)
    Typewriters, etc.
  - Monash-Younker Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1902; Uai +M743; 2 volumes (Box 184, Folder 2391)
    Automatic air valves
  - Monolithic Conduit Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1909; Uai M755; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2392)
    Conduit, etc.
  - Monroe Refrigerator Company (Lockland, Ohio), 1911; Uai +M757; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2393)
    "Monroe" porcelain refrigerators
  - Monsanto Chemical Company (Boston, Mass., etc.), 1939–1941; Uai +M758; 3 volumes (Box 184, Folder 2394)
  - Montgomery and Company, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai +M766; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2395)
    Machinery supplies
  - Monumental Bronze Company (Bridgeport, Conn.), 1883; Uai M769; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2396)
    Monuments
  - Moore and Nims (Troy, N.Y.), 1860; Uai M786; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2401)
    Globes, maps, and school books
  - Moore and Wyman Elevator and Machine Works (Boston, Mass.), undated; Uai +M7866; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2402)
    Elevators
  - Moore, E. R., Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1942; Uai +M781; 2 volumes (Box 184, Folder 2397)
    Choir gowns
  - Moore, Franklin, Company (Winsted, Conn.), 1923; Uai M782; 3 volumes (Box 184, Folder 2398)
    Chain blocks, trolleys, cranes, etc.
  - Moore, John (New York, N.Y.), 1882–1883; Uai M784; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2399)
    Horse blankets, lap rugs, robes, carriages, harnesses, etc.
  - Moore, John C., Corporation (Rochester, N.Y.), 1914; Uai M7842; 1 volume (Box 184, Folder 2400)
    Loose leaf books, ledgers, and cabinets, etc.
  - Morandi-Proctor Company (Everett, Mass.), 1938; Uai +M794; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2403)
    Cooking apparatus
  - Morehead Manufacturing Company (Detroit, Mich.), 1926; Uai +M815; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2404)
    Steam drainage and boiler feeding specialties
  - Morey Machinery Company, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai M818; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2405)
  - Morgan Crucible Company (London, England), 1882; Uai +M8232; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2408)
    Crucibles, muffles, etc.
  - Morgan Spring Company (Worcester, Mass.), 1908; Uai M824; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2409)
    Wire and springs, etc.
  - Morgan and Wright (Chicago, Ill.), 1899; Uai M823; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2407)
    Bicycle tires and equipment
  - Morgan and Wright (Chicago, Ill.), 1962; 7 volumes (Box 399, Folder 4328-4329)
    Tires, etc.
  - Morgan's, Enoch, Sons Company (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai M8246; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2410)
    Sapolio soap and cleanser
  - Morgan, D. S., and Company (Brockport, N.Y., Chicago, Ill.), 1886–1891; Uai +M821; 2 volumes (Box 185, Folder 2406)
  - Morris, I. P., Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1915; Uai +M832; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2411)
  - Morris, I. P., and De La Vergne, Inc. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1929; Uai +M8321; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2412)
  - Morris, Tasker and Company (Philadelphia, Pa., etc., 1873–1876; Uai +M833; 4 volumes (Box 185, Folder 2413-2415)
    Gas mains, iron products, photometers, etc.
  - Morrisville Milk Pan Company (Morrisville, Vt.), 1874; Uai M834; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2416)
    Milk pan and cooler
  - Morse Bougler Destructor Company, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1931; Uai +M837; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2417)
    Incinerators
  - Morse Chain Company (Trumansburg, N.Y.), undated; Uai M8372; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2418)
    Silent running high speed chains
  - Morse Machine Company (Rochester, N.Y.), undated; Uai M8376; 2 volumes (Box 185, Folder 2419-2420)
    Machine tools, drafting boards and tables
  - Morse Twist Drill and Machine Company (New Bedford, Mass.), 1896–1913; Uai M838; 2 volumes (Box 185, Folder 2421)
    Twist drills, reamers, milling cutters, etc.
  - Morss, A. S., Company (Boston, Mass.), undated; Uai M839; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2422)
  - Morton, George, and Company (London, England), 1899–1900; Uai +M842; 2 volumes (Box 185, Folder 2423)
    Anatomical, pathological, and museum jars
  - Moseley and Stoddard (Poultney, N.Y.), 1879; Uai M852; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2424)
    Cabinet creamery, dairy apparatus, etc.
  - Mosher, Martin J, (Troy, N.Y.), 1880; Uai M853; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2425)
    Laundry stove
  - Moss, Henry, and Company (New York, N.Y.), 1923; Uai M855; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2426)
    Rubber stamps, stencil plates, etc.
  - Mossberg, Frank, Company (Attleboro, Mass.), 1913–1935; Uai M8556; 3 volumes (Box 185, Folder 2427)
    Metal reels and spools, etc.
  - Motorstokor Corporation (New York, N.Y.), 1932; Uai +M857; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2428)
    Automatic coal burner
  - Motsinger Device Manufacturing Company (Pendleton, Ind.), 1903; Uai M8576; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2429)
    Auto-sparker
  - Mott, J. L., Iron Works (New York, N.Y.), Uai +M858
    Plumbing supplies, heaters, etc.
    - 1880–1900, 9 volumes (Box 197, Folder 2482-2487)
    - 1881, 1 volume (Box 198)
    - 1897, 1 volume (Box 199)
  - Mount Carmel Axle Works (Mt. Carmel Centre, Conn.), 1883–1905; Uai +M863; 3 volumes (Box 185, Folder 2432)
    Axles, etc.
  - Mount Carmel Axle Works (New Haven, Conn.), 1876–1893; Uai +M862; 4 volumes (Box 185, Folder 2430-2431)
  - Mount Washington Glass Company (New Bedford, Mass.), undated; Uai +M864; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2433)
    Inkstands, cut glassware, etc.
  - Mueller, H., Manufacturing Company (Decatur, Ill.), 1917; Uai +M887; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2434)
    Valves, water strainers, etc.
  - Muencke, Dr. Rob., G.m.b.H. (Berlin, Germany), 1910; Uai +M889; 1 volume (Box 208)
    Laboratory apparatus, etc.
  - Mulford, H. K., Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1912–1913; Uai M898; 2 volumes (Box 185, Folder 2438)
    Serums and vaccines, etc.
  - Mullins, John (Jersey City, N.J.), 1876; Uai M916; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2439)
    Furniture and carpets
  - Mullins, W. H. (Salem, Ohio), 1897; Uai +M9166; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2440)
    Architectural metal work
  - Multiple V-Belt Drive Association (Chicago, Ill.), 1944; Uai M9175; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2441)
    Power transmissions, etc.
  - Multiplex Display Fixture Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1934–1941; Uai +M918; 2 volumes (Box 185, Folder 2442)
    Steel display cabinets
  - Multipost Company (Rochester, N.Y.), 1926; Uai M9184; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2443)
    Mail stamper
  - Munger and Son (East River, Conn.), 1888; Uai M924; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2444)
    Blackboard materials, etc.
  - Municipal Engineering and Contracting Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1905; Uai M925; 2 volumes (Box 185, Folder 2445)
    Concrete mixers
  - Munising Paper Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1942; Uai +M9254; 2 volumes (Box 185, Folder 2446)
    Savings bonds, etc.
  - Munning, A. P., and Company (New York, N.Y.), 1919–1921; Uai M926; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2447)
    Electro-plating and buffing apparatus and supplies
  - Munning-Loeb Company (Matawan, N.J.), 1912–1923; Uai M9261; 7 volumes (Box 185, Folder 2448-2450)
    Lathes, plating salts, earthenware receptacles, etc.
  - Munson Gallery (New Haven, Conn.), 1942; Uai M927; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2451)
    Christmas cards
  - Munzinger, C., and Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), undated; Uai M929; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2452)
    Scientific instruments and books, etc.
  - Muralo Company (New York, N.Y.), 1899; Uai M931; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2453)
    Pounces and stencils, etc.
  - Murdock and Company (Boston, Mass.), undated; Uai +M941; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2454)
    Portable parlor grate
  - Murphy Door Bed Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1930; Uai +M958; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2455)
    Murphy in-a-door beds
  - Murphy Varnish Company (Newark, N.J., etc.), 1941; Uai +M959; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2456)
    "Da-cote" enamel varnish
  - Murray and Heath (London, England), 1867; Uai M967; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2458)
    Photographic apparatus, chemicals, etc.
  - Murray, James J., and Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1903; Uai M964; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2457)
    Globes and deflectors
  - Muskegon Chemical Fire Engine Company (Muskegon, Mich.), 1897; Uai M974; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2459)
    Ball bearing axles
  - Muzak Corporation (New York, N.Y., etc.), undated; Uai +M976; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2460)
    Music for work
  - Myer, F. E., and Brother Company (Ashland, Ohio), 1924–1938; Uai +M9926; 3 volumes (Box 185, Folder 2462-2464)
    Pumps, hay unloading tools, pumps, etc.
  - Myers and Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1878; Uai M993; 1 volume (Box 185, Folder 2465)
    Detergent